(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Okay, guys, this video is very important to
me.
It's just one thing I have to make
today.
Okay, guys, guys, I will not become what
soul to break me.
I will build what kind of healer soul.
You know, that's the policy on my system.
That's the very important policy.
That's the very important thing is that you
need it.
You don't want it.
You need it.
Any new implementation that goes through in the
very important thing is just like feed or
the shelter for housing.
You need that, you know, stability, you know.
There's no, human rights are getting better, but,
you know, the law and order around it
is getting better.
So, basically, I got my poem here.
It's not poem.
It's my story.
I got it here.
Look, guys, look at this.
I got to read this thoroughly.
I got to understand it.
You know, this, I'm okay holding up.
You got to understand what it really means
to me.
I'm going to cry about it.
I'm not going to cry about it, but
it's going to be about my history in
Nigeria and everything.
I'm going to give you the metaphysical, what's
it called?
That's all the story you want.
I'm going to read it.
I'm going to give you the message.
Now, this story is called Pandora's Box.
Pandora's Box, a fan section by me, Namdi.
Okay.
So, basically, I'm going to read this story.
I'm going to give you the other one.
But the goal of this is to have
more oral seal.
So, basically, this is an oral seal message.
It's like, you know, we have a private
key, not a public key.
You know, like, you know, the public keys
are the messages.
You know, the messages, you know, can be
like, the public keys can be like a
bliss poem.
But it's one message.
This is an oral seal for me.
But it's something called the reticle, like, you
know, in the reticle.
Like, you know, it's just rhetoric.
It means that you say a lot, but
it's just rhetoric.
You know, it doesn't mean anything.
It can mean something, but it doesn't have
to be, because it's just based on the
talk and what's going on at that time.
You know, it can mislead you, because it's
reticle.
It's not really the truth.
It can be somewhat true, but not true.
You get it.
But it's reasoning, about reasoning.
My own reasoning, the rationale behind doing it,
why are you doing that thing?
You know, why are you trying to adjust
the grand scheme of things at a small
scale?
You know, the minimal election alone.
This is an oral seal message I'm going
to give to you.
That's, you know, it's just that way.
I mean, how much does your lawsuit?
My lawsuit is $360 million.
I have to go to Cambridge to get
it.
But I have to go to Cambridge College,
because the Roth Code said no to me.
So basically, I'm building a legacy here, but
I'm doing it the right way.
I'm not like a rebellion in the wrong
way.
You know, I want to do my PhD
in the UK, but I don't think I
can do it no more.
And I don't want to go through the
bureaucracy.
But this story is really important to me.
It really means something to me.
Okay, okay, guys, let's just begin, because AutoAI,
oh, wait, oh, AutoAI is never recording.
Anyway, let's just begin, because this system is
kind of not recording, not recording.
Okay, it's not recording.
It must have stopped.
Anyway, anyway, it's not recording AutoAI.
And that's the problem.
Anyway, I've got my audio book.
Okay, no, no, no.
Okay.
Today is the Pandora's box.
Today, I will not become what is supposed
to break me.
I will heal, or heal us, or build
or heal us.
And that's part of all the policy systems.
If I'm ending as an invariant, I go
through the policy, I must heal itself.
You need to follow through with no education.
But I'm not supporting a lot of these
things.
Okay, this Pandora's box, my take, my fanfiction.
Okay.
The lady, Pandora, today, okay, today, okay, the
lady stared just at the box, never, I
was told, never to open it.
The box was these, the weapon, the evil.
She looked at, she looked at it.
She was, because the matter is ready, it's
already just right now.
That's what I'm really important.
She looked at it, she has a gaze
that her wonder about it, pondered about it.
And why her husband never told her to
open the box.
She was curious, Pandora.
She wanted to open the box, but she
never did.
Because of her husband, you know, the box
was open, was never to open.
It was sealed with locks and chains.
And I'm meeting because I'm making it up
because I'm going with the flow.
Pandora was to keep it in secret, to
hide it from the public view, and to
never show it or tell about it.
She was powerful, she was as powerful as
the man, as the husband, but she was
a woman.
She had a womb, she had to protect
and serve in other ways, but her husband
instructed Pandora to guard the box.
One day 25 years later, Pandora is 25,
by the way, her husband's friend came and
asked Pandora, your husband, have you seen him?
Have you heard of him?
Have you heard the news?
She answered, no, no, I've never seen him.
My husband came one week, in one week,
and talking to me one week ago, one
week before, he gave me this after fact,
he calls the box, and never opened it,
because she's 25, she's 15 now, and she
never opened it.
She answered to him, oh yes, the box,
yes, yes, why the box?
He said, she's kind of curious, she never
knew about it, you know, and the woman,
yes, yes, I know about that box too,
and the man replied, yes.
But he said, I should never, I'm not
going to talk about it, I don't know
nothing about any box, Pandora replied, she lied.
Then the husband says, don't worry, I got
evidence for you.
The husband's friend asked him, asked her, to
give away, that she's going to give him
all the keys to the box, to open
it.
Pandora, what?
You have keys to the box?
You know what this box contains?
Yes, but the husband replied, I have bad
news too.
Your husband, the Pandora's box says, yes, you're
my husband, what?
It's deceased, he died in the war.
What war?
I'm not sure of a war.
Oh Pandora, I'm sorry to tell you, but
your husband's deceased in the war, in the
war, the war happened one week before.
What?
Yes, didn't you hear it in the news?
Yes, the war happened one week before, they
had to go to the war.
The butterflies in the battlefield had to cease
your husband, he's deceased now.
But that was 25 years ago, he died
on the front lines.
So Pandora asked why he died on the
front lines, what happened?
Oh, the husband replied, it was a tragedy,
he got caught in the midst of the
madness and the chaos and the fire.
But that box was his seal, was his
aura, but he didn't abide by what was
there, set in stone, or do his job.
He was part of the royal monarchs, as
you know, he was part of the king's
leadership.
He was the one with the keys to
unlock the box.
And what Pandora replied?
He panicked.
So what's on the box?
The husband gave her the keys, the husband's
friend, sorry, gave her the keys.
And then gave Pandora at the time the
relief to do it in peace in her
own time.
The friend replied, your husband's aura
has not been sealed.
What does that mean?
Pandora asked.
You are part of the monarchs, part of
the most powerful family, that means the kings.
We have military control.
How could this have happened?
Pandora asked.
Pandora panicked and screamed.
And grabbed the keys on the structure man
to open the box containing Ashita Katan.
And his friends said, yes, here are the
artefacts to unlock this box.
It was sealed for a reason.
You need the time.
You need to radically reason, rational, about this.
You need to take your time to look
at the seal, to see why your husband's
seal was not sealed, and why his Christian's
master said no.
She thought just one week before, she heard
news about the war, and she read the
stories about the war with the newspaper article
in the box.
She opened it, and she saw that.
And then one week before there was a
war, before the war was announced, the next
week there was a war, the visual war.
She told nothing of it.
But then she opened the box to find
her husband was a military leader in the
war, in the colonial power system.
And she was his wife.
Now she's his spouse.
50 years later, she was 15 years old.
It's kind of interesting.
But she seems all her husband's power did
nothing to protect her and her legacy, or
the royalist petition of the people or the
corruption in Nigeria.
In the making, the legend of the making,
she threw the keys, and with the camera,
it's 25 years, November 2014 to 2011, 25.
With the camera, she opened the box to
see what her husband had sealed.
Guys, the box is sealed, because that's the
only thing he did.
And he went to do the job of
the human rupture.
25 years later, opened the keys, took the
box, and evil.
And she saw the news, the weapons, the
nuclear codes that was meant to be instructed
and guided and used according to the principle
of the protocol and the mortals, the missiles,
and the secret talks that was meant to
be accomplished.
But her brother was ignorant.
He didn't do this.
After confusion, after confusion, her husband started to
cry and would tears.
But why?
She knows enough.
She was confused about her husband and why
he didn't act.
But he did act, she thought.
She was confused.
She was paranoid.
But he went, but he never came back.
And next to confusion, she looked herself in
the mirror, when she got her box from
her house.
And she was concerned, shocked, and she began
to cry, tears.
She's going to look herself in the mirror,
a reflection of her soul, her spirit, or
her soul, you know, as a child, you
know, who she was.
She cried.
She stared at herself.
She became what?
Broke them.
The change started with them, but now I
transcend that change with us.
That's me.
Guys, that's what an oral seal means.
You know, that's just an example.
These guys have put that, these two oral
seals like this, so basically, as a child,
I go through the broken system, blah, blah,
to reflection of myself, of what is yet
to be and become.
I became, as an adult, an adult of
journey back to becoming a king, because what
am I trying not to do with others?
I'm an adult, 25.
I'm going with Nigeria.
I don't have a house in the UK.
I don't really care.
But I'm a British Nigerian passport.
As an adult, I go back to the
broken system to, yo, fix that thing.
And that's all the broken infrastructure there.
You know, this is Pandora's box by me.
And I'm the brother.
The change started with them, but I transcend
that change with us.
I will not be, also, to break me.
I will build, work in your soul.
And that is the world's first life, work,
constitution, live, work, breath constitution.
You know, you live there, you work there,
you breathe there.
You know, there's no, there's no structure.
The infrastructure is broken, and it's against you
by design.
By design, not by, not even by the
token, not only by direct construction, but how
it's built is fragmented.
It's fragmented.
For me, this is, like, how I want
to do it.
Because I see problems in Italy.
You know, I see patterns in the city.
There can be problems, you know.
I can reach my way through the system,
but you guys can't.
You know, you just have a battery in
the green cup.
You don't have to mess up.
This is my will.
I'm going to move again.
This is my lawsuit.
This is what it means.
You know, it wasn't my wife, you know.
And this happened to me.
I would tell my wife, like, you know,
if that's the one I care about, I
don't have a wife or a friend or
girlfriend, you know.
I would tell her, look, this box is
very open.
But don't keep it in secret.
You know, if I die or something happens,
you must take charge.
I really see the problem.
Because, you know, so you can have this
seal.
You know, everyone can solve this problem of
this missile crisis, you know.
Because, you know, the different war is terrible.
Because, you know, remember, well, it's not a
drug.
It was terrible.
It was 50 years.
In fact, it took me to the last
three years.
But there's not a decreshing date.
So the date between us, you know, there's
been five years.
Now it's 50 years.
Now the situation has passed.
The situation has passed.
I am now holding a torch.
I'm not a torch bearer, you know.
Don't worry about Nami Kano.
Nami Kano doesn't understand what I'm doing.
I'm doing something else.
I'm doing stuff.
I'm actually building stuff.
You know, he's like doing stuff.
He's like my one.
I'm a rebel.
But I'm not in the rebel in that
sense of the word.
I'm a rebel.
But I'm in the right way.
You know, I'm repairing the way that cannot
be broken down easily.
You know, that's what I'm saying.
I'm telling you, this is the birth 19th
of May, 2001.
1905, you know, Generation Z, Gen Z.
You know, go Gen Alpha.
You know, those people in Nigeria, they're fucking
up the whole time.
They're messing things up.
This is Pandora's backs.
Pandora cried.
She rubbed and shuddered.
And the tears bled until she passed out.
You know, she became a maniac in the
end.
You know, she became a mechanic.
Because, you know, the infantry did not sustain
her.
And she just got older and died.
Why?
Because no one 25, 50 years old is
too old for Nami Kano.
You know.
You know, I mean, people like young women,
you know.
But, you know.
In Nigeria, you can get 50 million times
in a different manner.
But you have to have stability.
You know.
She's not stable.
She can be powerful, yes.
But she doesn't have that alignment.
Because the government around her has changed.
Everything has changed.
You know.
She can't get anyone.
If she wants to marry or have a
child.
It's not that bad.
That has to.
That has to mean the story.
That's it.
For the magical implication.
That's what it means to have an aura
seal.
You know.
Their aura was a change.
Their change was us, was them.
You know, them.
But them was not us.
You know.
We are different from them.
That's what it's them.
Us.
We can be them.
But you know.
Them doesn't mean us.
Because you know.
I want something.
We are against each other.
And this is the real world.
You know.
We are fighting against systematically.
By design.
By how fragmented the ecosystem is.
How you can buy carbon.
Buy food.
I can't find water.
You know.
That's kind of thing.
I want to heal as well.
You know.
I want this as a policy.
In that thing.
And everything invariant wants to be.
I'm going to put that there.
Sorry, no sir.
Everything is inferior.
I want to cover the foundation.
You know.
My constitution.
Don't worry about the summit.
At least by killing people.
I don't want to kill people.
I want to build people.
You know.
If I can.
It's not about empathy for me.
I'm not.
I'm a competition.
I'm a scientist.
It's about end result.
And that's what I'm saying about.
You know.
I don't have to fail you.
I know.
I'm autistic.
As per just.
This is what this law system means to
me.
My greatest capacity.
My healing begins.
My journey.
My time is now.
My healing begins.
You know.
I'm not talking to you guys.
I'm talking to myself.
This is for a moment for myself.
You know.
I'm not being.
I don't care.
I don't have values.
I don't know who's the beast.
Who wants me to be.
You know.
I have a room.
You want to see my room?
No.
Come on.
I'm here for you.
Anyway.
Look.
I'm part of a mentor.
I have ADHD.
As per just autism and disability.
And this autism stuff.
Talking about the modern body.
And we shouldn't have.
What is it.
What's stop.
They can't do anything.
They must stop.
I'm seeing those people.
I can see you.
I'm not seeing people that don't do that
to me.
You know.
And I'm going to leave this UK.
And when I come to Nigeria.
I'm going to fix this.
My aura.
I have to seal my aura.
I have to build what.
What can heal us up.
And I will do that.
I'm going to trust you that change, that's
what you're doing to enjoy the killing of
all the evil people, black people, and this
like what I do, because I'm a king
there, I'm king of the navy, I'm a
member of the states, I'm a member of
the, you know, I'm going to build, I'm
going to heal, heal, sustain us of the
Bfrens, you know, the Bfren, uh, uh, uh,
Iwu, uh, Iwu constitution, uh, uh, uh, means,
uh, public, uh, Iwu, IWU means low, and
uh, Oda means, uh, an IJE, that's IWU
OHA, uh, public, uh, UWU, um, low, uh,
IJE Lola, separation of concern, uh, principles, repositories
at github.com, slash OBNACAS, thank you.
My name is Namdi Abala, and this is
the world's first design and technology, health and
social care, uh, breath to life, to work,
uh, constitution, built on human centricle principles, around
the humans, phenomenological, lens, principles, as a fundamental
protocol for, for, uh, for defragmentation of an
ecosystem that failed an entire, two entire generations,
actually, that's 25 years and 25 years too,
there it is, thank you for watching.
Like, share, subscribe, maybe on my youtube too,
my tiktok, etc, just like, okay,
this is still going, so if it's a
velocity, you're done.